<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Findings on UVA Biocomplexity Institute</title>
    <link>/findings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Findings on UVA Biocomplexity Institute</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/findings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Section One</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-one/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3 { text-align: center; }  Main Findings Dadashazar (2017) identified factors including previous incarceration, family relations, employment and education barriers, housing constraints and substance abuse to be associated with increased recidivism. Hanson (2017) concluded that prior criminal history and substance abuse were among the risk factors for multiple types of recidivism across multiple types of offenders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Section Two</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-two/</guid>
      <description>Main Findings Economic Vulnerability may also be affected by health and education accessibility. Those with access to health and education facilities were less likely to be poor and vulnerable (Gil et al., 2014). We measured health and educational access separately in each Virginia County using multiple indicators. The health indicators correspond to hospitals, clinics, counseling centers, and other health facilities that are immediately in aid of a vulnerable population.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Results Section Three</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-three/</guid>
      <description>Main Findings Factor Analysis and Social and Economic Vulnerability Index Page county is a rural county in the Valley region in Virginia. While factor analysis and composite index construction have been done on different scales, we are limited by our data to the county-level. However, other social and economic modeling approaches were applied to county level data and were developed to address shortcomings of predecessor models (Cutter et al., 2003).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/findings/isochrones/hospitals__virginia_shp/read/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/isochrones/hospitals__virginia_shp/read/</guid>
      <description>hospitals</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/findings/isochrones/read/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/isochrones/read/</guid>
      <description>isochrones</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/findings/isochrones/virginiashapefiles/read/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/isochrones/virginiashapefiles/read/</guid>
      <description>shape files</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>